あっ！　このファンデ 欲しかったやつ！
Hmm... No problem.
こっちのリップと スプレーマニキュアもお願い！
You can bring out tanks and fighter jets.
あ　このウイッグ　かわいい！ ボス そろそろ出発の時間ですよ。
I will stop them all.
エリザは何も買わなくていいの？
He's following the road.
ええ　私は何も。
If he continues on it,
he'll pass by in ten minutes.
あっ…。 あれ　かわいかったね
Do you think he'll stick to the road?
似合ってた！ よかったよね。 トイレに行って来る。
No, he'll notice my presence
just before he gets here.
あっ　いいよ 荷物　ちゃんと見ててね。
Because APR will start adding interest again.
クラピカの奴 あのままで平気かね？
But given his speed...
体のほうは　私の笛で 少しは回復したと思うんだけど。
We may be able to attack him
just before APR adds interest. I Alone Lose When It Reaches the Heavens
Chapter 7 Bankruptcy
暗殺の話は　お前　どう思う？
Knuckle's ability, Chapter 7 Bankruptcy, attaches APR to an enemy.
((「十老頭」は 「旅団」の始末をプロに依頼した))
Every ten seconds, APR informs the
enemy that interest will be added.
) ((クラピカ　その殺し屋のチームに 参加してもらいたい))
But if the enemy is over a hundred meters
away from Knuckle, the interest stops.
心音を聞いた限り 全てを納得した上で
When this happens, the time
until the next interest payment is remembered by APR.
暗殺チームに 合流したわけじゃないわね。 だろうな。 でも　クラピカには 何ものよりも先立つ決意がある。
Once the enemy is back within
Knuckle's hundred-meter range, APR picks up where it stopped.
自分の全てを犠牲にしても それを優先している 結果の判断だと思うわ。
He's approaching at a speed between
160 and 180 kilometers per hour.
ダルい生き方だな。 俺にゃ　マネできん 自分を殺す人生に意味あるか？
If there are still three seconds or more
before APR adds interest again, there's a good chance we can
attack before he notices us.
お嬢様　遅いですわね。
Here he comes!
人生いろいろ
Damn, what happened?
何に重きを置くかは 人それぞれだわ。
At the last second, he suddenly changed direction!
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…！ あ？
He's down below! Knuckle...
どうしたの？
Don't bother. We can't catch up.
お嬢様が　いません！ えっ？ 何!?
Our opponent has a cheetah's speed.
パパのウソつき！
He isn't supposed to know
how to deal with Zetsu.
うまいこと言って　本当は私を
How did he discover our ambush?
オークションに 連れて行きたくないんだわ！
Could it be...
入れ。
Look up! What's that?
ひの　ふの　み　よ いつ　む…。
I've discovered two suspicious figures. What should I do? Ignore them. They aren't the target.
全員　揃ったようだな。 いや　まだだ。
No point in doing more work than necessary.
ん？　チームは８人のはずだろ。 ノストラードが １人　新たに連れて来るそうだ。
Yes, sir. It appears they were trying
to ambush Cheetu-sama.
チッ！　あのインチキ占いの オベッカ野郎か。
Oh, he's in the area? I warned Cheetu-sama before he ran into their trap.
依頼は「幻影旅団」の抹殺。
This is Leol.
今夜　再開される競売に 奴らが　また来るかもしれねえ。
The target just engaged a squad of
soldiers in the city of Longtong.
現れたら始末してくれ やり方は任せる。
Longtong? Head north and try to cut it off. Just a hunch.
一応　同じ標的を狙うチームだ。
Understood.
連絡の際の 呼び名を決めておこうか。
Looks like even the army can't handle this.
色でいいだろう 俺はブルーと呼んでくれ。
No... Well, they're only there to buy time.
俺はレッドで…。
They've had to stay in one area
for a longer period of time.
ん？　お前らは？ シルバ。 ゼノじゃ。
After all, it's been moving constantly
for over thirty hours.
何？
Diego has fallen into enemy hands!
俺の名を呼ぶのは自由だが 指図は受けない。
If you stay in your homes, you'll be killed! Liar!
俺達のやり方でやる。
Rebel scum!
シルバ　ゼノって… まさか　ゾルディック家か？
Damn... Diego just appeared on TV,
looking alive and well.
同業のよしみで ３割引きで請け負うぞ。
I'll have to give up my instigation. My only option is to take out as many
puppets and soldiers as I can!
彼らがキルアの家族…
Should I go north next?
しかし　あの「旅団」だぞ 単独でやるには　ヤバ過ぎる。
I knew it. Someone's still following me!
あんたは？ 拙い連携は　混乱を招くだけだ 私は一人で十分。
Who's there?! If you want something, show yourself!
フッ…　５対４　決まりだな。 オークションの開始は９時 会場までは　我々が送る。
The presence has completely vanished. It might be following me until
more Chimera Ants show up. I'm gonna shake it!
それまで待っていてくれ。
It can't outlast me!
よう　ノストラード 調子は　どうだ？
Yo... Yo. Sorry for stopping you.
まぁまぁだ。
Nah, I was headed this way.
まぁまぁねぇ… 偉くなったもんだぜ。
The King's in this direction, right, Hagya?
つい　この間まで　片田舎の いち組長だった野郎が
Yeah, I know. It's Leol now.
今じゃ　この俺と タメ口きけんだからなぁ。
Then you did that on purpose? You're still a bastard.
何でも　もみ手のし過ぎで 手を　やけどしたそうじゃねえか。
Flutter's warning was a big help.
大丈夫か？　アハハ…。
Right now, I'm trying to avoid fights... I'm glad to hear that.
男のジェラシーは見苦しいな。
By the way, what's that thing?
ん？　てめぇ！
No idea. A Hunter hit me with it.
何だ？　この野郎　あ？ 刺すなら刺してみろよ　ごらぁ！
It follows me wherever I run. Not sure what to do.
クラピカ　やめろ。
But so far, it doesn't seem to have any effect.
言っておくがな 誰も　てめぇらなんぞ 認めてねえからよ！
Do you want me to get rid of it?
俺の成功を妬む奴が多くて困る
I'm glad you're so understanding.
だが　俺は　まだまだ上へ行く
Figured. The Royal Guard has assigned me a mission.
ネオンの予言を駆使してな
I'd like your help.
お前の働きには期待している。
Leol-sama...
十分な見返りは用意するつもりだ。
I've spotted the target.
ええ。
He's headed north on the road through
the forest northeast of Longtong.
警察署長は その市長の子飼いの男だ。
We're chasing down a human. He's probably a Hunter.
交通規制くらいは朝飯前だよ。
And you want me to help hunt him?
[TEL]
You said he's a Hunter?
もしもし。
They can be tough to deal with...
[TEL]　クラピカ　大変！ ボスが逃げちゃったの！
Of course, so I've planned ahead.
トイレで着替えた上で 逃げてるから 計画的みたいなのよ。
Shaiapouf-dono has prepared
a power tailored for you.
だとしたら　行き先の見当はつく。
He will teach you to use it.
ホテルに戻って待機してくれ。
With luck, you can master it in a day.
どうした？ お嬢さんが逃走したそうです。
I'm a slow learner, so mine took me
three days to get the hang of.
何!? 行く先は　我々と同じでしょう。
Sounds like a sweet deal...
オークションか！
In return, I swear loyalty to the King?
クソ！　電源を切っている。
Exactly... Easy enough, right?
だが　ネオンは 参加証を持っていない。
Sure, I just wanted an explanation.
会場どころか検問で　はねられる。
You're a sharp fellow.
ライト＝ノストラードだ 検問中の全警官に指示を頼む。
If you accept, return to the castle, master your new power,
and then contact me.
参加証を持たない １７１８歳くらいの娘が
In the meantime, I'll have my underlings
determine the target's abilities.
検問所に来たら保護してくれ！ 特徴は…。
Well, I guess I owe you one. Might as well.
ＯＫです　どうぞお通りください。
Anyway, you're still all about stealing glory.
よかった
Naturally.
検問　通れなくて困ってたの ホントに　ありがとう。
I was once king of the jungle.
どういたしまして。
Obviously, you're looking to retake the throne.
[TEL] 本当か!?　それは　いつだ？ ほんの５分前です。
Damn, I'm being followed.
髪形と服装は　データと 少し違いましたが　恐らく。
And he's way out of yo-yo range.
[TEL]　参加証は 持っていなかったんだな。
If I don't lose him or defeat him, I'll be in trouble.
「でも　私のパパは…」と 言いかけて
There's a jungle over there!
結局　引き返して行きました。 はい　タクシーに１人でした。
The leaves are dense enough, he shouldn't be able to see me from the air.
[TEL]　はい　失礼します。 ご苦労さま。
If he descends to follow,
he'll be in range of my yo-yo!
市内の地図は　ありますか？
He isn't coming? Did I lose him? But in that case, he should
come looking for me.
えっ？
I don't have time to wait around! Hurry up, already!
誰だったかな…
You can't hide from me.
得意だよ 偉い人にも頼まれるし
Go forth, soldiers of Leol.
どれくらい当たるの？ 百発百中なんだって。
Capture your prey!
「なんだって」って… 君が占ってるんでしょ？ 勝手に手が動いちゃうの。 へぇ　すごいね！
Something's coming, but from the opposite side, and it's on the ground!
どれどれ？ クロロ＝ルシルフル 変わった名前ね。
He removed his foe's head
and arms with one swing! I can't beat him in a one-on-one,
close-quarters fight...
アハハ！　何それ　もっと変！ フッ。
Captain! Above you!
オークション会場の セメタリービルの中にいますね。
I'm gonna die—
はい　できたよ。
We're attacking him en masse, in the treetops,
and we can't even touch him! Retreat! Time to regroup!
見ていいかな？ もちろん！
I won't let you escape...
私の占いって変わってて ４つか　５つの ４行詞からなってるのね。
You must be the leader. I'll eliminate you first!
へぇ。
How'd you like that blast?
あ…。
I'd guess he has a power that
lets him track my location. In that case...
すごいね　合ってるよ。
I can't show him the cards
in my hand, no matter what.
この１つ目の詞なんだけど…。 えっ？　あっ　ダメダメ。
I don't want them to learn
of my lightning or yo-yo!
私ね　自分の占い　一切見ないの。
The ideal scenario would be to lose
them and go back into hiding.
どうして？
But that's looking impossible.
なるべく 自分が　かかわらないほうが 当たる気がするから。
I'll have to defeat them all without using—
じゃあ １つだけ聞いてもいいかな？
A gun?
うん。
No...
この詞には　死者の鎮魂を 想起させる部分があるんだけど
There's something stuck to my face...
君は　死後の世界ってあると思う？
A flea?
占いは　あくまで 生きている人のためのもの…
この場合は　クロロさんのね。
Damn!
もし　そういう表現があったなら
Where did it come from?!
慰められるのは霊じゃなく あなたのほうだと思う。 確かに　そうかもしれない。
Area TH-88, X-15, Y-12, Z-2.
行こうか　そろそろ オークションの下見の時間だ。
Point X-9, Y-3, Z-1.
小さい頃　テレビで見た 占い師が言ってたの。 「占いは　今を 一生懸命　生きている人を
There's no escaping...
幸せにするためのもの」って。 そう。 だから　その占い師は なるべく悪いことばかり
from my Fleadom, oh yeah.
「そうすれば　みんな そうならないように
Damn!
願ったり 努力したりするでしょ」って。
The bleeding won't stop.
私　その時　「ああ　そうだな」って すごく感動しちゃって。 それから ずっと占い師に憧れてたんだ。
These fleas are more than just big bugs... Area P-9, Y-7, X-8, Z-4. Point Y-5, X-3, Z-1.
何年かして　その占い師の人 詐欺罪で捕まったんだけど。
And when you factor in...
ひょっとして「銀河の祖母」？ そうそう！ そういえば　彼女は 死後の世界　否定派だったね。 そうなの だから　私も信じてないんだけど。
my air gun's power, they become unstoppable, oh yeah.
えっ？
No wonder those apes couldn't do anything.
だから　死んだ　そいつが 一番やりたがってたことを してやろうと思ってね。
If I keep running around, it'll be
harder for them to snipe me!
何それ？
But I have to conserve stamina.
あっ！　大丈夫ですか!?
Ah, he's going to try something.
早く医者を呼んでくれ！
He may try to use his power.
こちら　１階北側エレベーター前。
Let's see what he can do.
[TV]　急病人だ　救急車を。
Okay.
[TV]　ノストラードファミリーの 娘さんだぞ！ [TV]　てめぇ 責任とれんのかって伝えろ！
My Super Eye allows me to observe a target
チッ！　聞こえたよ 「十老頭」にもファンがいるからな。
from multiple angles via my Satellite Dragonflies.
仕方ねえ　手配する！ おい　救急車を呼べ！
No ability you use can escape my sight.
はい！ このモニターの 画面だけを巻き戻して
Now, let's see what you do.
恐ろしく早い手刀… 俺でなきゃ　見逃しちゃうね 久々に血が騒ぐぜ…
Killua cannot use En. Expanding his aura around him
and maintaining it for a long time
俺の獲物だ
is by no means his forte.
５階の５０１号室で 休んでいるそうです。
And so, he keeps his aura within
the range he can best manage.
参加証を手に入れるツテなど ないはずなのに 一体　どうやって…。 お嬢さんの写真が ハンターサイトにアップされています。
In other words, the moment a projectile is
within fifty-seven centimeters of his body, Killua must rely on his incredible reflexes
何？ 恐らく　ハンターサイトで お嬢さんの写真を手に入れ
and physical strength to react
with desperate speed, and dodge at point-blank range.
近づき ここへ連れて来た人物がいます。 捜し出して　ぶっ殺してやる!!
But this time, he didn't dodge!
落ち着いてください。 恐らく　相手の目的は お嬢さん自身ではない。
All to determine the angle of
the projectile's approach.
例えば　ビルへの侵入に際し
Damn... It came from this way!
ここにいては危険です。 センリツ達には　連絡しました もうすぐ来るでしょう。
He let himself be hit, so he
could locate the sniper.
奴らに任せて大丈夫なのか？
The target is quickly heading your way.
ボスも一緒に ついていてください。
Okay.
ありません。 ここは戦場になります。
I somewhat expected this.
オークションは また中止になるでしょう。
The bleeding's stopped anywhere
that the fleas only scratched me.
血の道しるべ わざと垂らしておく
They must secrete some chemical that
stops blood from clotting naturally. If I start bleeding in too many
places, I'll be in trouble.
同類にのみ分かるように 香るように
I can't let him escape!
仲間だ　お前は
This is perfect.
俺と同じ　殺人中毒者
I can see clearly in every direction. How do you like this? There's nowhere for you to hide!
安心しろよ つまらないトラップは使わない。
Bring it on!
ああ。
Wait!
団長からだったよ。
This desert is massive.
「セメタリービルで 暴れるから来い」言ってるね。
If you don't have any water,
you'll die of thirst in a day.
考えること同じね
Too bad...
ゴミ掃除しながら ビルに向かってるね。 よし　それじゃ行くか。
I wanted to observe you a little longer, but I guess that won't work.
あと　団長が珍しく 暴れ方に条件つけたね。
I was running low on stamina, anyway.
条件？　何て。
I suppose this gives us more
time to talk things over...
)
Let's begin with introductions.
「大切な暦が一部欠けて
Because you'll be a valuable partner.
遺された月達は 盛大に弔うだろう。
You have business with the King, right? I do not! Huh?
喪服の楽団が奏でる旋律で
That was dangerous...
霜月は 高く穏やかに運ばれて行く。
He must have a reason for approaching me. I can't tell him anything.
菊が葉もろとも涸れ落ちて
Really? Aren't you guys here to defeat the King? "You guys"?
血塗られた 緋の目の地に臥す傍らで それでも あなたの優位は揺るがない。
Yep... I've been watching you since
that other kid was with you. I understand.
遺る手足が半分になろうとも。
And you felt that I would put up
less of a fight than Killua!
幕間劇に興じよう。
Huh? Eh?!
新たに 仲間を探すもいいだろう。
You've got it all wrong! That's how you interpret it?
向かうなら東がいい。
I guess it makes sense...
きっと待ち人に会えるから」
To you, I'd look like an enemy. I guess I should clear up the misunderstanding first.
ハッハッハ…。
I swear that I'm not lying. I'm not looking to trick or defeat you!
ハハハ…　おい　なぜだ。
Okay, I believe you.
ハハハハ！　なぜだ!?
Of course... It's hard to believe! I can sympathize.
なぜ俺は　まだ生きているんだ？
If I were in your shoes... Eh?
この魚は 「インドアフィッシュ」といってね 閉め切った部屋でしか 生息できない念魚だ。
Is that him?
ハッハッハ… 死なない…　フッフッフ。
This is a trap. You still wanna come?
ヒッ…。
I'm impressed!
「大切な暦が一部欠けて
Blood! Food! It's food!
遺された月達は 盛大に弔うだろう。
Wait, this is...
喪服の楽団が奏でる旋律で
Captain Ikalgo's host! Crap, stop eating it.
霜月は 高く穏やかに運ばれて行く」
I want to stop, but I can't... The blood is calling to us!
俺達からのレクイエムです
I couldn't let you drag me into the water. These suction cups saved me.
血で血を洗う壮絶な
Anyway, aren't you an octopus?
しかし　どこか悲しみに満ちた 嵐の夜が始まった
Don't call me an octopus! Killua's opponent turns out to be Ikalgo, a parasitic Chimera Ant, resembling
an octopus, that uses human hosts.